2023-08-28 03:45:07 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of text theme' start 2023-08-28 03:45:07 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-08-28 03:45:33 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-08-28 03:45:33 INFO - Session id - 78eeded34ee1b5ab59242325a06abfbd429f765a 2023-08-28 03:45:33 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-08-28 03:45:33 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:35 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-08-28 03:45:36 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-08-28 03:45:36 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:36 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-08-28 03:45:38 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-08-28 03:45:38 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:40 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:45:40 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-08-28 03:45:43 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:43 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-08-28 03:45:44 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:45 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:46 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:47 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-08-28 03:45:48 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:48 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:50 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:51 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:45:52 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000002 2023-08-28 03:45:52 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - bookName: Cryptonomicon Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - bookName: Phantom Lover Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - bookName: The Black Kids Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - bookName: Legacy Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - bookName: The Innovators Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - bookName: Goliath Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 6 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:45:53 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000002' 2023-08-28 03:45:54 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:45:54 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-08-28 03:45:56 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:46:02 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:46:03 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-08-28 03:46:24 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:46:24 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-08-28 03:46:24 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:46:47 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-08-28 03:47:07 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:09 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Palace Marketplace' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-08-28 03:47:09 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-4 2023-08-28 03:47:09 INFO - randomBookName: Two Girls and a Guy 2023-08-28 03:47:09 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-08-28 03:47:10 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'Two Girls and a Guy' 2023-08-28 03:47:12 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-08-28 03:47:15 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-08-28 03:47:16 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:47:16 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:23 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-08-28 03:47:24 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:47:24 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:25 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-08-28 03:47:25 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:26 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-08-28 03:47:26 INFO - Scrolling 8 times on reader epub screen 2023-08-28 03:47:45 INFO - Step 15 - Open font settings 2023-08-28 03:47:45 INFO - Button 'btnFontSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:46 INFO - Step 16 - Change contrast to BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE 2023-08-28 03:47:46 INFO - Button 'setThemeLight' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:46 INFO - Step 17 - The BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE background is correct 2023-08-28 03:47:47 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-08-28 03:47:47 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-08-28 03:47:48 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-08-28 03:47:49 INFO -

The Geometry Lesson

by Dave W

With a certain resignation, he reached out his hand and turned off the bedside lamp. In the dark, his hand brushed over the other side of the bed, which was untouched. This kind of physical reminder that he was alone was, of course, completely unnecessary. A confirmation that his evening had turned out to be a failure.

He had to admit, though, that it was his own fault.

He had been looking forward to Petter’s visit for a long time. Petter was one of his best friends, and now that he was living abroad, they didn’t see each other very often. He was one of their best friends, actually. Christine was crazy about him. And really, it hadn’t been unusual for him to go to sleep alone and leave the two of them sitting outside, with something to drink and plenty to talk about. But that night, he had been hoping for – no, counting on! – something more. The last time Petter had come to visit, the evening had taken an unexpected turn, one that he had so often fantasised about. Petter had chosen the music. Soon the three of them had were dancing around together, to Katie Melua’s sensual beats. And before he knew what was happening, they had let themselves be carried away by a wonderful threesome, in which Christine had fulfilled her secret dream of having two lovers at once – and a probably more secret dream of making love with Petter... Well, perhaps, he had dreamed about it more often than her. But still, was it so crazy to expect that the situation could repeat itself?

The evening had gotten off to the worse start. Christine had probably tried to drop a few hints before that, even though he had tried to remain blind. Hadn’t she given him a sign already after that first time, letting him know that she had felt pushed into the game? That indeed it had been him to suggest it, and she hadn’t liked being manipulated like that? Hadn’t she let him know that he shouldn’t expect this to become a common occurrence? Also, right before Petter got there, she had said straight out that she didn’t want any strange allusions. Thomas had felt attacked and had tried to defend himself. It had just made things worse. She had just cried back that he was “obsessed with sex” and that there was no way this night was going to take an erotic turn. He gave up, of course, but he was in a terrible mood and didn’t quite manage to hide it. And although they had a pleasant dinner, he had dropped some ironic hints that Petter had tried to brush off, but which had probably offended Christine. Eventually, he’d said that he had an early morning the next day, and had gone to bed.

So now he lay there alone in the double bed, feeling annoyed, both at himself and at Christine. Lying in the darkness, upset and frustrated, sleep just wouldn’t come.

“I’ll come to bed soon, too,” she had said as he left.

But she hadn’t come. They sure had a lot to talk about, those two. Or was something else going on? Not that he really believed it. But after a while, as the minutes ticked by, he became more and more obsessed with finding out. Over half an hour had gone by. Finally, he stood up, put on his robe and slid out into the hallway outside the bedroom.

The moment he opened the door, he realised that something was going on. He heard Katie Melua playing on the living room stereo. As quietly as he could, he moved in the direction of the sweet music that brought back so many erotic memories. The living room was dimly lit. And in the middle of the room, he saw the two of them move in a slow dance. Christine had her arms around Petter’s neck, her face buried against his shoulder. Her blouse was open, and he could see how one of Petter’s hands was massaging her large naked breasts. He almost couldn’t believe his eyes. She pressed up against his body as the sensual music played. She lifted her face up towards him. Their lips met in a long, deep kiss. Now he noticed that her trousers were also unbuttoned, and Petter’s hand was moving down from her breasts, stroking her naked stomach, before it disappeared between her thighs, under her trousers and panties. Christine writhed and sighed lightly when he found her most secret spot, that by now was surely wet and smooth and warm against Petter’s searching fingers. Thomas could almost feel it.

He was fascinated by what he saw. It was a beautiful and sensual scene – it was incredibly arousing to see Christine like that. He was turned on, and he felt his cock begin to stiffen underneath the smooth robe. At the same time, he felt a pang of jealousy. Not because Christine clearly wanted Petter and was acting according to her desire. He had been the one to take the initiative, the first time. But now, she was cutting him out. And not just that; she had actually told him that nothing erotic was going to happen tonight, but then she’d gotten going as soon as he’d been out of sight! But wasn’t it also exciting? He actually wanted her to be freer, he wanted that for her! Now his cock was pounding hard, and couldn’t help but grab it as he watched the other two embrace in an increasingly intense dance, right there in front of him, on the living room floor.

How long could he stand there and look at them? He thought about letting them know he was there. Maybe they’d let him join the game? But he pushed the thought away. They wouldn’t like it, they’d feel interrupted, revealed, it would ruin it all for them, but also for him in a way. Should he just stay there and see how far they would go? Count on the fact that they wouldn’t realise he was there? He felt a bit like a voyeur, a strange guilty conscience as if he were the one doing something wrong by spying on them, and not those two out on the dance floor. And all the while, he was more and more turned on.

Then, suddenly, it was no longer up to him to decide. Christine turned her head in his direction, he didn’t dodge quickly enough, so she looked right at him, in the doorway where he stood. For a moment, he wondered what he should say or do, to help her and all of them out of this awkward situation. But Christine left him no time to think. She freed herself from Petter’s arms, pulled her blouse around her naked breasts, and in a few long steps, she was standing in front of him and looking strictly into his eyes.

What are you doing here?”

Thomas was completely taken aback and didn’t manage to answer before she went on:

“I thought you said you were going to bed? Yet you’re standing here, spying on us? Controlling me?”

He tried to protest, in a weak, stuttering voice.

“Come on, Christine, this is...”

But she cut him off. “I have no intention of discussing this with you here. Let’s go to the bedroom!”

And then she grabbed his ear as if he were a disobedient schoolboy, as she turned towards Petter:

“I’ll be back soon – I just need to get this settled, first!”

Thomas saw how Petter, looking a little flustered, remained standing there and watching them as she dragged him down the hall.

Confused, he let his wife’s hard grip lead him on. He didn’t manage to decide what he should make of this situation, not to mention how he should react before they reached the bedroom.

“Take off your robe! Get in position!” Christine commanded.

This was a command Thomas was familiar with – it wasn’t uncommon for them to play erotic games based on this type of old-fashioned punishment, and indeed, they were often very exciting. But what kind of game was this? He nevertheless obeyed, almost automatically, and bent over, naked, supporting himself with his hands on the bed. And he couldn’t help but realise that Christine’s unexpected reaction had only turned him on even more. Game or no game, his cock was throbbing hard against his stomach, as he stood there leaning over in this humiliating position. He heard Christine open the closet where she kept the cane they usually played with.

“I’d thought you might want to come and spy on us,” she said coolly. “That you might not actually be quite as open-minded and relaxed as you want to sound when you say I need to feel more erotic! That, indeed, you want to be in charge. But now, you’ll learn that I am the one who decides and that this kind of behaviour deserves a punishment!”

And then she swished the cane in the air and smacked his naked butt hard. He cried out and tried to get up and couldn’t help but rub the spot where the stinging cane had hit him.

“Back into position!” Christine ordered, cold as ice. “You remember our rules, don’t you? You must stay in position until I inform you that I am done!”

Slowly, he bent forward onto the bed again. He was beginning to realise that something new was about to happen between them and that he couldn’t nor didn’t want to stop it. The cane came swishing down again, and again and again... Christine punished him with the stinging stick, systematically, until his ass was burning hot and sore. He desperately tried to obey her orders and not move a muscle as the whole thing went on. Eventually, she was done, and she commanded him to go stand into the corner of shame.

He heard her fumble in the closet again but didn’t dare turn around to see what she was happening. Then he felt her coming behind him, sneaking a hand in front of him and grabbing his hard cock.

“Now I’ve let Petter wait long enough,” she said briskly. “You stand here, and no matter what happens, you can’t turn around or change position until I tell you so.”

He nodded, without speaking. She squeezed his cock hard and continued:

“And since you are so horny, I must make sure you won’t be tempted to play with yourself while you’re standing here.”

Then she pulled his arms behind his back, and moving quickly, she placed a leather cuff around each of his wrists and hooked them together. He heard her walk out of the room and down the hall again, towards the living room.

Thomas didn’t know what to think or to believe. His thoughts kept revolving around what was going on in the living room, and his jealousy was growing by the second. Now they had really cut him out! But in a way, hadn’t she also included him, with this new form of the game? A game that turned him on. There was no doubt about it. His cock was throbbing hard, he felt an almost irresistible urge to touch himself, but it was impossible, with his hands tied behind his back. Of course, he could have escaped if he had wanted to; but standing there, obediently, like Christine had ordered to, was even more arousing to him. Christine’s new game was so captivating.

The minutes crept forward. In the distance, he could hear the sensual music playing in the living room, filling his mind with images of the two involved in hotter and hotter games. Then suddenly he heard steps in the hallway, coming towards the bedroom. Did they want him to join them, at last? What had Christine said to Petter? Had she told him about the cane? He could still feel the sting burning in his butt, and the fiery red colour of his buttocks would surely reveal what had happened. The thought that Petter would see him standing like that felt surreal. But he also knew that he neither could nor wanted to spoil the game. Now they were inside the room. He was about to turn towards them, but he remembered what Christine had said. Regardless of what happened, he had to wait for new instructions. He forced himself to stand still in the corner.

Nobody spoke. But he heard the sounds of their heavy breathing, their deep kisses, warm, wet, hungry. He heard the sound of clothes falling to the ground, of hands grabbing each others’ bodies. Their arousal filled the room. He heard Christine falling onto the bed. With all his senses – except his sight – he felt Petter following after, between Christine’s naked legs. Thomas could almost physically feel how Petter moved his face up towards her open, warm pussy. He heard the sounds of his friend’s tongue against his wife’s wet, smooth labia; of Christine moaning in pleasure. Petter’s tongue had found her clit. Perhaps one of his hands was massaging her soft breasts, rubbing her stiff nipples just like he himself used to do. She breathed faster and faster, louder and louder. Was he also sliding a finger inside her, all the way to her most secret spot? Now her whole body was tensing around him, Thomas knew it, he felt it, she was getting close, and then he heard her cuming, when she cried out her lust, gasped in the throes of a violent orgasm, a long one, yes, ohhhh, yeeeeees....!

Thomas was in a trance. Miles away, he heard Christine cry out that she wanted Petter inside of her. And then she barked a command that dragged him back to reality:

“Thomas, turn around! Now you must look!”

He turned around, slowly, towards the two lovers on the bed. Feeling impotent and turned on at once, he saw Petter kneeling before his naked, beautiful wife, with his large, wonderful hard-on swaying eager above her. Christine spread her legs further, she got ready to take him in. Infinitely slowly, Petter sank down towards her. Thomas watched as he pushed inside her, dove deep into her open, hungry pussy while she put her legs around him and welcomed him in. They began to move together, rhythmically, as Petter thrust harder and faster in and out of her, Christine moaned in pleasure, cried out a few incomprehensible words, she clung to him, as the ride became more intense and violent. Petter was breathing louder and faster now, Thomas could almost feel his friend’s climax coming close. And then he looked as Petter gave in to his pleasure. With a long, low cry he came, and Thomas knew that Petter was shooting his hot load inside his wife, while his own hard-on throbbed helplessly as he stood and watched.

At the end of an exhausted embrace that seemed to last hours, Petter pulled out of her. Christine looked at Thomas, her eyes full of horniness and a kind of teasing tenderness. “Come here, my love,” she said. Slowly, he walked towards the bed. He stood in front of her, his hands still tied behind his back. She reached out and grabbed his throbbing cock. She carefully began to jerk him off, pulling his foreskin back and forth over his tip that was dripping with a clear liquid.

“Seems that you liked what you saw,” she said softly. “Maybe it’s your turn now?”

He wanted to answer, but she stopped him.

“No, don’t say a word! Just listen to me!”

With her hand around his cock, she kept jerking him off slowly, as she continued.

“This is just a little lesson to be learned, you see. A geometry lesson. You are so interested in triangles, I understand. And tonight I want to teach you something important. There are many types of triangles. Not all are equilateral. Triangles with me are not equilateral. I am the one who decides. You have learned this, haven’t you?”

She squeezed his cock hard, as he nodded silently, feeling that he was reaching the point of no return. She noticed it as well, and let go of him.

“This turned me on again,” she said with a teasing smile. “I want a cock inside me again.”

Thomas felt that the desire to get inside her almost overwhelmed him, and he leaned forward towards her. But she stopped him.

“No, not you, not tonight. I want Petter’s cock inside of me.”

She turned partway around towards Petter, who was lying behind her on the bed. He had been following the whole scene with great attention. Her hand grabbed his cock, which was already half-stiff again. She looked up at Thomas:

“But if you obey me completely, I’ll let you find your release eventually... I want to see you suck Petter for me, hard, Thomas! And if you two truly understand that my desire sets the rules, then you’ll let me see this...”

Thomas met Petter’s gaze. This was completely new. And what about Petter? Did he want this? Petter smiled, gently and encouragingly. They were both completely overpowered by Christine. Slowly, Thomas bent forward over the bed and brought his face close to his friend’s cock. He opened his mouth and closed his lips carefully around his cock. It was an incredible feeling, unlike anything he had ever felt. The warm, wet cock tasted of Christine’s juices, but also of something different, strange. He took it deeper in, moved his mouth up and down along it, growing bolder and more determined, then he tried to suck, thinking about what he himself liked when Christine did it to him. And then, what a wonderful warm feeling, he felt his friend reacting, his cock slowly beginning to grow inside his mouth, coming to life, becoming larger and harder.

Christine smiled and looked at them. Her eyes shone with lust. One hand had made its way down between her thighs, and with skilled fingers, she was playing with herself. Now Thomas felt that his friend’s cock was rock-hard. He gently pulled back, and with a sense of humiliation mixed with desire, he told himself that he had obeyed. He had gotten Petter ready to fuck his own wife again. Christine turned over to the side, with her back to Petter, and lifted one leg a bit. Then she grabbed his hard-on and pushed it inside herself from behind so that Thomas could see the whole thing. And as Petter started thrusting his massive cock in and out between her open, shiny, smooth labia, she reached out her hand and grabbed Thomas’s throbbing cock again. His hands still tied behind his back, he kneeled helplessly before the two lovers on the bed and let her jerk him off, and without taking his eyes off Petter’s cock sliding in and out of Christine’s hungry pussy, he felt his orgasm building up inside him. His whole body shook, as horniness took over him and he came. With a cry, he shot his juices out over the bed.

Christine looked at him for a long time, a new tenderness in her eyes.

“I think you’ve learned enough geometry for tonight, Thomas,” she said softly. “Turn around!”

She freed his hands.

“There is a bottle of champagne in the fridge,” she continued. “Go get it. And glasses.”

He stood up, looked at her. She read the unspoken question in his eyes.

“Yes, you can fetch three glasses,” she smiled. “This triangle is not equilateral, but it still has three sides.”

Then she led her fingers down to her pussy while Petter continued thrusting rhythmically in and out of her.

On the way back towards the bedroom, carrying the champagne bottle and three glasses on a tray, Thomas heard Christine cry out her pleasure again, in a new, violent orgasm. As he walked in, he saw that Petter was also coming again, with a final deep thrust inside her. He stood in the doorway for a moment, holding the tray, and let the image of the two lovers on the bed sink in. It turned him on again. The night wasn’t over. And with a teacher like that, he was looking forward to continuing studying.

2023-08-28 03:47:49 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-08-28 03:47:49 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-08-28 03:47:51 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-08-28 03:47:52 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:55 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:56 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:57 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:47:58 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:47:59 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:48:00 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:48:20 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:48:21 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-08-28 03:48:21 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@2d706ff3

2023-08-28 03:38:34 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of text theme' start 2023-08-28 03:38:34 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-08-28 03:39:00 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-08-28 03:39:00 INFO - Session id - c43ddfc137cd4c013cc8da4413dc54868f9bea96 2023-08-28 03:39:00 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-08-28 03:39:00 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:02 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-08-28 03:39:03 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-08-28 03:39:03 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:03 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-08-28 03:39:04 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-08-28 03:39:04 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:05 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:39:05 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-08-28 03:39:08 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:08 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-08-28 03:39:09 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:10 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:11 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:13 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-08-28 03:39:13 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:13 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:14 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:15 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:16 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000002 2023-08-28 03:39:16 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - bookName: Goliath Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - bookName: The Black Kids Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - bookName: Phantom Lover Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - bookName: Cryptonomicon Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - bookName: Legacy Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - bookName: The Innovators Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 6 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:39:17 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000002' 2023-08-28 03:39:18 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:39:18 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-08-28 03:39:20 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:39:26 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:39:26 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-08-28 03:39:47 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:39:48 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-08-28 03:39:48 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:40:10 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-08-28 03:40:30 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:40:32 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Bibliotheca' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-08-28 03:40:32 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-3 2023-08-28 03:40:32 INFO - randomBookName: Santa Cruise 2023-08-28 03:40:32 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-08-28 03:40:33 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'Santa Cruise' 2023-08-28 03:40:35 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-08-28 03:40:37 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-08-28 03:40:38 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:40:39 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:40:45 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-08-28 03:40:45 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:40:46 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:40:46 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-08-28 03:40:47 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:40:47 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-08-28 03:40:48 INFO - Scrolling 7 times on reader epub screen 2023-08-28 03:41:07 INFO - Step 15 - Open font settings 2023-08-28 03:41:07 INFO - Button 'btnFontSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:08 INFO - Step 16 - Change contrast to BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE 2023-08-28 03:41:08 INFO - Button 'setThemeLight' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:09 INFO - Step 17 - The BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE background is correct 2023-08-28 03:41:10 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-08-28 03:41:10 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-08-28 03:41:11 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-08-28 03:41:11 INFO -

Chapter One

June
Ridgewood, New Jersey

The big banner read WELCOME RIDGEWOOD HIGH CLASSMATES! For some, it was a frightening experience. For others, it was an opportunity to show off how far they had come in the fifteen years since leaving high school.

Francesca (Frankie) Cappella was on the fence. She had built an excellent reputation in the publishing industry, marketing books for authors and publishers, but her love of music and the desire to perform had never left her. After graduating from a top music school, she had spent six years in New York City, auditioning for every part for which she thought she was suited. She had a “big voice” with a lot of nuance, but the producers were looking for a big nasal voice, something that made her cringe. Sure, she could sing that way if she had to, but she hated it. Why would she want to do something she hates? It took all the pleasure out of singing for her. Eventually, every singer sounded the same. She had spent too many years working on her own sound. Taking matters into her own hands, she found a producer and cut a few tracks. She got some radio airplay, but without the backing of a big record company, she could only go so far. During the years she had spent following her dream, to pay the rent she had worked as a temp for a number of large corporations, eventually taking a full-time job with a publisher of comic books. Her parents knew that working in corporate America wasn’t in her heart, but it was a living, and living in New York was challenging enough.

She eventually worked her way up to the top at a major publishing house, but she never felt as if she was a success, especially after the incident at the last reunion, when Drew Aikens said something right to her face. “Gee, Frankie, you were such a good singer. Too bad you never made it.” Those crushing words almost kept her from coming to this reunion, which included several classes besides hers. Still feeling the sting of those hurtful words, she thought to herself, Maybe that creep won’t show up.

Frankie knew that some would be envious of her position as a vice president of a successful publisher. Her life was interesting and filled with a lot of professional events, but she still felt that a piece was missing. A lover, a partner, a friend. Sure, she could have three different men, but what she really wanted was a man who was all three. Yeah. Good luck with that.

She took one more glance at her reflection in the glass of the hotel artwork. Hair? Jet black, slicked, and pulled into a long ponytail. Dress? Figure-flattering little black dress that showed off her well-toned calves. Lipstick? Bright. She then had the horrifying thought she might have lipstick on her teeth. Next came the angst of her eyeliner running. But before she had the chance to pull out a small mirror, the squeals of Nina Hunter were heard across the lobby.

“Frankie! Oh baby.” Nina Hunter pushed through the crowd and gave her friend a huge, crushing hug.

Nina was five feet eight inches tall, towering over Frankie’s five-foot-four-inch frame. In high school, Nina had been in every school play, community-theater production, and summer-camp program. That’s where she and Frankie had bonded. Frankie was the singer; Nina was the actress. Nina’s love was acting, and she was particularly good at it, so much so that she had landed a part on a television sitcom after attending the University of Southern California. She wasn’t the star of the show but had enough screen time to make her a fan favorite. Her long brown curly hair, big brown eyes, and long legs were hard to miss.

“Nee-Na,” Frankie howled back, making sure her makeup didn’t smudge on Nina’s silk dress. “I wasn’t expecting to see you here!” Frankie was surprised but also tickled pink.

“I have an audition in the city in a few days, so I thought I’d return to our old haunts.”

“You mean Shut Up and Eat?” Frankie joked, referring to the local diner where they would hang out after football games or other school events. Only the coolest kids would go there.

“Is it still there?” Nina asked.

“It is. Butch Anderson organizes breakfasts there several times a year,” Frankie replied. “I’ve been to a few; but to be honest, I don’t feel I have anything in common with them anymore.”

“I think I know what you mean.” Nina put her arm around her friend. “It’s married couples talking about either their latest renovation or bragging about their kids.” Nina made a snoring sound, causing Frankie to burst out laughing.

“Oh my goodness. You are so right.” Frankie nodded in agreement. “I feel like the only thing I talk about is work or some function I’ve attended. They look at me as if I’m some kind of snob. Or weirdo.”

“I totally get it. If I’m not surrounded by Mr. and Mrs. Whoever, it’s someone in the biz blowing smoke about their latest script, treatment, and who might be reading it next. I mean, it is Hollywood, but it can be so superficial.”

“I can only imagine,” Frankie said. “I had a small taste of it when I was trying out for musicals. Funny thing, though, publishing isn’t all that different. It’s a sliver of show business. Besides, most of the publishing companies are owned by big conglomerates. But enough of that. Tell me about you. Besides your acting success, what else keeps you out of trouble?” Frankie chuckled.

“My dog.” Nina smiled. “He’s a big Bernese mountain dog named Winston. We go for hikes in the hills. He makes me feel safe on the trails even though he’s really a mush.”

“I assume you live in a house?” Frankie asked.

“Oh yeah. I cannot imagine Winston in an apartment. It would be like a bull in a china shop!” Nina chuckled. “I rent a small house in Topanga Canyon. It’s just far enough from the hustle that I can drain my brain after long days of shooting.”

Glancing at the posters covered in student photos, Frankie said, “You’re probably the most successful graduate.”

“Oh, I don’t know about that. Yes, I am incredibly lucky to have landed this part, and I mean incredibly lucky. It’s really about being in the right place at the right time.”

“Speaking of being in the right place, I think I may need to go to the bar and get a little something to soothe my nerves.” Frankie linked her arm through Nina’s.

“Nervous? You?” Nina was surprised. “You were the ringleader, party thrower, class president, lead singer in a band, and captain of the gymnastics team.”

“That was before I knew anything about life.” Frankie laughed. “Back then, I thought if you went for something and gave it your all, you’d be rewarded. And if you tried really hard but made a mistake, all would be forgiven, and you would get another chance. Nope. You make one mistake, and it goes into your permanent record.” Frankie used air quotes for “permanent record.” “This grown-up stuff isn’t easy.”

Nina burst out laughing. “Kinda like you make one creepy low-budget film to try to get exposure, and you’re pegged as ‘Oh yeah, that Nina Hunter. Didn’t she play a disembodied creature in that hack movie?’ ”

The women howled and continued making their way toward the bar. As they waited in line to be served, Frankie whispered to Nina, “Who are these people?”

Nina let out a guffaw, then whispered in return, “I think we went to high school with most of them.” She ordered a gin and tonic for herself. “Frankie? What are you having?”

“Hemlock?” Frankie chortled.

“Ha! Wine? Or a stronger adult beverage?”

“I’ll have what you’re having,” Frankie replied, and Nina held up two fingers to the bartender.

Frankie lowered her voice further. “They all look so frumpy! Sure, you would expect that of the people who graduated a few years before us, but even our own classmates! Most of them look like they gave up caring years ago.” She nodded to a woman wearing clogs. Nina almost spit out her drink.

“Oh my gosh. That’s Amy Blanchard. She hasn’t changed a bit.” Before either of them had an opportunity to say hello to Amy, a loud cry came from the throng.

“Ladies!” It was Rachael Newmark, one of their old pals, doing a little rumba dance in their direction.

“Honey!” Nina gave her a one-arm hug, trying not to spill her drink. “You look great! Still dancing, I see?”

Rachael Newmark was the shortest and most petite of the three, with a brown pixie haircut, turned-up nose, and green eyes. “Chicas! So good to see you. You both look fabulous.”

They immediately huddled and joked that they were not old enough to be at the reunion.

Amy caught a glimpse of the three women and started in their direction. “Well, if it isn’t the unholy trinity,” Amy teased.

Frankie bit her lip, Nina was taken aback, and Rachael couldn’t help but blurt out, “I see the fashion police haven’t been here yet.”

Amy blinked. “Oh these?” She pointed to her feet. “I broke my toe and, quite frankly, I don’t give a darn.”

“When did you ever?” Rachael said, with a touch of sarcasm.

“Good point,” Amy agreed. “But I’ll have you know that it’s quite the geek fashion statement now.” She took a bow.

All four women laughed. Amy had been the geek, dweeb, nerd of the group. She was president of the science club in school but had a lot of team spirit and would always sign up to be the stage manager for the plays. She would often get teased because she was much more the intellect than most of her classmates, but Nina, Rachael, and Frankie always included her. They would refer to Amy as “the brains of the operation.” She still wore the same big black-rimmed glasses. Her ash-blond hair was adorned with a pink headband that matched her maxi dress. She had a pretty, round face with a milky complexion and rosy cheeks. There was a spunk and youthfulness about her that belied her age of thirty-three.

Nina took the lead. “Well, ladies, perhaps we should grab a table before we’re forced to sit with some creep from biology class.” They all laughed, recalling Billy Gwyer chasing the girls around with a garden snake.

“Do you think he might be here?” Frankie surveyed the room.

“The big question is, is he as cute as he used to be?” Rachael snickered.

“You were always boy-crazy.” Amy poked at her.

“And look where I am now,” Rachael replied. “I got married because my parents didn’t want me running all over the world chasing men. And how did that turn out? Well, now I’m divorced.”

“But are you still chasing men?” Nina joked.

“I’ve given up.” Rachael sighed.

“You?” they mocked in unison.

“It’s slim pickings out there, girls. Even old Slim Pickens himself is no longer available.”

The women hooted. “I hear you loud and clear.” Frankie joined in. “I haven’t had a date—I mean a real date—in probably three years.”

“You can’t be serious.” Nina crowed. “Look at you. You’re stunning and successful.”

“Thanks, but that doesn’t seem to make for a great date, let alone girlfriend. My friend Ken once told me that I’m very intimidating.” Frankie shook her head. “I don’t get it. I’m so charming.” She smiled wryly.

“Honey, I’m in the same single boat,” Nina confessed.

“But you’re in the land of glamour and excitement,” Amy protested.

“It’s a lot of smoke and mirrors. Trust me,” Nina replied. “If I were a high-powered producer or an agent, I’d have a new date every night. But unless you can do something for someone, you’re not dating material.”

“I don’t believe it,” Amy objected. “You, famous actress, can’t get a date?”

“I’m not that famous,” Nina said.

“Well, you are to us,” Amy insisted.

“Yes, you are,” Frankie added, and Rachael agreed.

All eyes were on Amy. “So? What about you? Have you found geek love?” Nina asked.

“Nah. Most of the guys I meet are asexual or indifferent.”

“Funny how things change. When we were in high school, we had to beat the boys away with a stick.” Frankie laughed.

“That’s because you weren’t so intimidating back then.” Rachael poked fun at her friend.

They leaned conspiratorially toward each other, ignoring everything that was going on around them, and caught up on the past fifteen years.

After high school, Rachael Newmark had attended NYU. After she graduated, she had traveled to South America, where she met a suave but unemployed Paulo. With her trust-fund maturity on the near horizon, her parents clamped down on her escapades, forcing her father to hire a private jet to bring her back home. Following weeks of pouting, Rachael realized that if she ever wanted the money left to her by her grandmother, she needed to think about settling down. The thought sent chills up her spine, but reality had set in. She took a job at a bank, working in their international department, and began dating one of the accountants. She wasn’t madly, passionately in love with Greg, but he was steady and would be a good provider. Love was not her parents’ main concern. Stability was. A year later, they got married.

Two years after getting married, they had a son, but being a stay-at-home mom just wasn’t her thing. She was restless and needed a purpose, something Greg couldn’t understand. Greg left the bank and went to work for an independent accounting firm. Rachael’s parents thought it would “look better” for Greg in their social circle if he worked at a high-powered company. If she wanted, Rachael could be a local socialite, join the garden club or the Junior League. But Rachael’s personality was not compatible with women who were prim, proper, and phony. Especially phony.

Before Ryan started school, Rachael would arrange playdates with other moms and kids, but after a period of time, she would get bored with the vacuous conversations and move on to another group.

By the time Ryan entered kindergarten, Rachael was ready to climb the walls, so she took a part-time job at the local dance studio. She had always been an excellent dancer and had taken lessons in jazz, ballroom, and a variety of other disciplines. By the time she was eight, her parents had her schedule completely filled. Dancing lessons, piano lessons, tennis lessons, and water skiing were planned. Tutoring in foreign languages was also on her calendar. It was no surprise that she had rebelled after graduating.

Of all the extracurricular activities, it was the dancing that made her feel alive. She could lose herself in the music and the moves. Plus, it was important to know how to dance, especially when you had to attend galas and fundraisers. It wasn’t surprising that she was everyone’s favorite dance partner.

Within two years of working at Salon de la Danse, her classes became so popular that there was a six-month waiting list if you wanted to learn to salsa, rumba, or swing. People of all ages were clamoring for Rachael’s dancing excitement.

But when Rachael was home with Greg, the only excitement was the argument du jour. It became obvious that their marriage wasn’t going to last, at least not without a lot of door slamming, yelling, and sulking.

Finally, after an uncomfortable dust-up at the country club, Rachael’s family intervened and encouraged her to get a divorce. They could see the pain in their daughter’s eyes whenever she and Greg would meet them at a social event or dinner. Her father took her aside and said, “Sweetheart, your mother and I have been talking.” That sentence was always a warning signal, but this time it worked to her favor. “We can see how unhappy you are, Rachael. I know your mother and I pressured you into getting married and having a family. But we never expected it to make you this miserable. It’s the last thing we want. We will help you with whatever resources you need, particularly a good lawyer.”

Rachael was shocked and elated. Never in a million years did she think her parents would approve of a divorce. You made your miserable bed and now you have to lie in it was a much better summation of their take on life. But getting married hadn’t really been her choice. She had been pressured into it. Yes, her parents wanted stability for her, but they hadn’t counted on the misery that went with it.

Aaron Newmark was a man of his word and provided Rachael the counsel of the best divorce attorney in the state, Lloyd Luttrell.

She and Greg tried to keep the divorce civilized, although Rachael was always seething when it came to Greg. Over the course of their marriage, Greg had spent a good chunk of Rachael’s trust fund buying luxury cars and expensive designer clothes. That, too, caused a great deal of contention. He said it was important to look rich. No one was going to trust a poor-looking accountant. He had a point, but he had carried it much too far. He was supposed to be the breadwinner and she the dutiful wife, whose half-million-dollar bank account was at his disposal. As soon as the smell of divorce was in the air, Rachael’s father and her lawyer tied up all of her assets so Greg could no longer treat them as his personal piggy bank. They sold the elaborate McMansion they had bought with part of Rachael’s trust fund and put some of the money away for Ryan’s college education. Greg was lucky to get out of the marriage with the fancy designer shirt on his back.

To that day, Rachael had never had a total grasp on how much of her money he had milked. She knew she was complicit by not paying attention. But still. It was not his money to spend.

Once the divorce was final, Rachael used the rest of the money from the sale of the house to buy the dance studio from its owner. She renovated the space and hired more instructors, and the studio doubled its clientele in less than a year. It helped that she was located near a senior-citizen community with most residents only in their midfifties. Part of the studio’s service was planning dance parties for organizations. Rachael had finally hit her stride.

The women stared at Rachael. Nina was the first to speak. “Wow, he really took advantage of your family’s money.”

“Oh, that’s not all.” Rachael tossed her head back. “He was cheating on me the whole time.”

Screams of “What?” “Are you kidding?” “You can’t be serious!” went around the table.

Rachael crossed her arms across her chest. “No, I’m not kidding, and yes, I am serious.”

“Holy smokes!” Amy broke in. “How did you find out?”

“It all came out after the divorce. A few people knew about it, but no one had ever told me. And frankly, I do not care. I had no physical interest in him at all.” She paused. “Probably ever.” She burst out laughing. “Talk about stupid choices.”

Frankie chimed in and lifted her glass. “What doesn’t kill you makes you stronger!” The rest followed suit, uttering words of cheer.

It was now Frankie’s turn to catch the women up on her escapades. She had moved to New York after graduating from the University of Miami. She auditioned for musicals and got a few small parts in Off-Broadway shows, but that and temp work paid very little, forcing her to live with a variety of roommates, two to three people at a time. One summer, Frankie rented a bedroom in a large two-bedroom apartment on the Upper West Side. They had divided it up so that Dave and Laura would have the living room as their space, Marilyn would have the other bedroom, and they shared a ridiculously small kitchenette. It wasn’t ideal, but it was doable for the few months she was there.

Finding a suitable place to live was a full-time job. She eventually moved into a duplex with a work associate and stayed for several years until she was able to afford a modest studio apartment in Gramercy Park.

Frankie and Rachael had stayed in touch and met for lunch a couple of times a year, so they were familiar with each other’s horror stories. Rachael was getting impatient and urged Frankie, “Cut to the chase. We want to hear your stories. I know you have a few lulus.”

Frankie took a deep breath. “Are you sure you want to hear the gory details?” Nina and Amy urged her on. Frankie confessed that she had been through a boatload of relationships, affairs, heartbreaks, and deceptions. New York. Lots of men. It was easy to meet someone at a bar, club, event, or concert. Learning about someone was another story, especially with most New Yorkers her age coming from all parts of the country and the rest of the world. She often thought it was ironic that someone could be in the biggest city in the country and still feel lonely and isolated. That’s probably why she was eager to have something meaningful with someone. Too bad she had made a lot of lousy choices in her pursuits. Frankie continued, “Then there was the medical intern who had not one but two other girlfriends.”

“Two?” Amy gasped.

“Yes, two.” Frankie took a sip of her drink.

“How did you find out?” Amy was curious.

“I had spent the night at his apartment. The next morning, he left before me. I opened the door to the linen closet to get a towel.”

“Oh sure. You were spying.” Rachael poked her.

“No. Honestly,” Frankie continued. “I was getting a towel and noticed a small container on one of the shelves.” She took a sip of her drink. “It was a diaphragm.” Another sip, waiting for a reaction from her friends.

“A what?” Amy blurted.

Nina patted her hand. “Oh, honey. It’s one of those contraceptive contraptions that women use so they don’t get pregnant.”

“I know what a diaphragm is. Duh,” Amy shot back. “I was kidding.”

Nina patted her hand again and turned to Frankie. “So what did you do?”

“I did what any other red-blooded woman would do. I took it with me and threw it in a dumpster several blocks away.”

The women were doubled over in hysterics. Frankie continued, “I never said a word to him. I figured he would be squirming enough when she went looking for it.”

Nina was laughing so hard, tears were streaming down her face.

“Did he call you?” Rachael tilted her head.

“Yes, he did.” Frankie played with the small straw in her glass.

“Spill, girl!” Amy was almost shouting. “What happened?”

“I didn’t answer the phone but he left me a voice mail saying how immature it was of me to take someone else’s property.”

Amy’s mouth was agape. “He said what?”

“You heard me. But, I must say, I got a lot of satisfaction out of that call. He was so pissed. Too bad, too sad. Such a jerk.”

“So how did you know he had been seeing two other women?” Amy asked curiously.

“A friend of mine. One could say it was a coincidence, but think about this. New York City has a population of eight million people, and over ten thousand doctors.”

Nina pushed, “Get to the good part!”

“As I was saying, a friend of mine was introduced to him at a hospital function. He was with a woman named Victoria. Well, while they were chitchatting, a woman named Michelle walked up to him and slapped him in the face.” Frankie sat back in her chair with a wry smile.

“Wow.” Nina gasped. “Well, at least he got the slap he deserved.”

“Yeah, too bad it wasn’t from me.” Frankie chuckled. “I felt vindicated without having to do anything except dispose of something gross. It’s funny. Odd, I mean. I wasn’t angry. I was stunned. But when I tossed that thing in the garbage, I felt elated just thinking about how he was going to talk his way out of its absence.”

“He sounds like a real piece of work,” Nina observed.

“Yes, indeed. I pity his patients. Now he’s a psychiatrist.”

The women almost spit out their drinks. “Seriously?” Amy barked.

“Yep.” Frankie nodded. “I feel like I dodged a bullet with that one. And several others, I suppose.”

Silence fell across the table.

Frankie’s eyes twinkled. “I have an idea.”

“Uh-oh,” Amy said.

“I know we all hate Internet dating . . .”

Nina held up her hand. “I am going to stop you right there, girl. There is a NO DIVING sign at the dating pool.” The women laughed.

“Seriously. Listen,” Frankie went on. “Let’s make a pact. I know this is probably something we swore we would never do. But”—she took a deep breath—“if none of us have dates for New Year’s Eve by this Thanksgiving, we’ll go on a singles cruise together.”

“What?” Nina’s eyes almost bugged out.

“Huh?” came from Amy.

“Count me in,” Rachael said, jumping at the idea.

“Really. What’s the worst that can happen? We’ll have fun, get a tan, and come home with some duty-free perfume,” Frankie assured them.

“That could be fun,” Nina agreed. “It’s only June now, so we have plenty of time to either ruin our lives again with a man or get ourselves into bathing-suit shape.”

A groan went around the table. “OK. So we’ll wear sarongs,” Nina added.

“And cover-ups,” Amy said.

“And big hats,” Frankie suggested.

“Let’s not forget the dark sunglasses.” Rachael put her two cents in.

“Caribbean?” Frankie asked. “We can meet up in Miami and take one of those four-or-five-day singles cruises. Come on! Like I said, the worst that can happen is we get a tan.”

“Or tossed in the drink for being too rowdy.” Nina chuckled.

Rachael clapped. “I love it!”

“Don’t get too excited there, missy. We’ll keep you on a tight leash,” Nina said.

“Ha. Isn’t the whole point to have some fun?” Rachael protested.

“Absolutely!” Frankie was pleased with her idea, and her friends were enthusiastic about it, too. “It will be like The Love Boat with eggnog.”

The women reached across the table and grabbed each other’s hands. “Pinky swear!” They locked fingers the same way they had in high school when they set out to accomplish something.

Frankie surveyed the room. “I think our work here is done. Are any of you staying here at this hotel?”

“I’m at my folks’,” Amy replied.

“I’m at a B and B off Henshaw Drive,” Rachael said.

“I’m at the Courtyard,” Nina put in.

“Oh good. So am I. I couldn’t get a room here, which is fine. I don’t know if I want to keep running into people I don’t remember,” Frankie said almost apologetically. “Let’s go over to the Courtyard and hang out. I don’t see anyone or anything worth pursuing here.” She giggled.

“Splendid idea,” Nina agreed.

“Pajama party?” Amy almost begged.

“I have two beds in my room. You can join me, but won’t your mother be upset?” Frankie asked.

“You mean my mother and Mister Charm? Nah. They’re at the club. I’ll send her a text so she won’t worry.”

Rachael frowned for a moment. “Can I come and play, too?”

Nina put her arm around Rachael. “Sure thing, babe. I also have an extra bed.”

In unison, they high-fived each other, grabbed their purses, and headed toward the door when a loud voice came over the speaker. “Let’s all say hello to the famous Nina Hunter!”

Hoots and applause filled the room.

“Uh-oh. I thought we could make a quick getaway,” Nina said with clenched teeth, feigning a smile. “Hello, everyone!” She made her way up to the podium while the three other women waited near the exit.

“It’s so nice to see all these familiar faces,” Nina lied, with a big, bright smile. Frankie was stifling a laugh. Then Nina said, “Let’s have a round of applause for the reunion committee. Didn’t they do a great job?” Lots of clapping, whistling, and cheers filled the room. Once the noise subsided, Nina ended her impromptu appearance with, “I trust everyone tunes in on Thursday night for a half hour of laughs and crazy family fun! See you on the boob tube! Enjoy the evening! Be safe!” She gave a wave and stepped away from the microphone as the group gave her the appropriate applause. She hustled toward her friends to make a quick getaway in case other people wanted to talk to her. In spite of her big personality and her love for theater and acting, Nina was basically shy. She said it was her acting skills that helped her deal with people.

As the four women exited the hotel, Frankie pulled up her Uber app and ordered a car to pick them up. When they got to the Courtyard, they raided the minibars in their rooms, settled in, and made plans for their seafaring adventure.

2023-08-28 03:41:11 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-08-28 03:41:12 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-08-28 03:41:13 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-08-28 03:41:14 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:17 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:18 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:19 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:20 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:41:21 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:41:21 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:41:42 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:41:42 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-08-28 03:41:42 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@2d706ff3

2023-08-28 03:08:32 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of increasing and reducing the text size' start 2023-08-28 03:08:32 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-08-28 03:08:58 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-08-28 03:08:58 INFO - Session id - 5bdbf637f3b7ce69effe520d20e01b06f0c9f51a 2023-08-28 03:08:58 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-08-28 03:08:58 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:00 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-08-28 03:09:01 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-08-28 03:09:01 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:02 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-08-28 03:09:03 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-08-28 03:09:03 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:06 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:09:06 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-08-28 03:09:09 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:10 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-08-28 03:09:10 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:11 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:12 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:15 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-08-28 03:09:15 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:17 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:18 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:19 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:20 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000002 2023-08-28 03:09:20 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - bookName: Cryptonomicon Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - bookName: Phantom Lover Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - bookName: The Black Kids Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - bookName: Legacy Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - bookName: The Innovators Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - bookName: Goliath Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 6 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:09:21 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000002' 2023-08-28 03:09:24 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-08-28 03:09:24 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-08-28 03:09:26 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:09:32 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:09:33 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-08-28 03:09:55 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:09:55 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-08-28 03:09:56 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:10:18 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-08-28 03:10:38 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:10:40 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Palace Marketplace' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-08-28 03:10:40 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-1 2023-08-28 03:10:40 INFO - randomBookName: A Bottle of Old Wine and Four More Stories 2023-08-28 03:10:40 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-08-28 03:10:41 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'A Bottle of Old Wine and Four More Stories' 2023-08-28 03:10:44 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-08-28 03:10:54 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-08-28 03:10:55 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:10:56 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:04 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-08-28 03:11:05 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:11:06 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:06 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-08-28 03:11:07 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:08 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-08-28 03:11:08 INFO - Scrolling 8 times on reader epub screen 2023-08-28 03:11:38 INFO - Step 15 - Save font size as 'fontSize' 2023-08-28 03:11:38 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-08-28 03:11:38 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-08-28 03:11:40 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-08-28 03:11:40 INFO -

A Bottle Of Old Wine

Richard O. Lewis

Herbert Hyrel settled himself more comfortably in his easy chair, extended his short legs further toward the fireplace, and let his eyes travel cautiously in the general direction of his wife.

She was in her chair as usual, her long legs curled up beneath her, the upper half of her face hidden in the bulk of her personalized, three-dimensional telovis. The telovis, of a stereoscopic nature, seemingly brought the performers with all their tinsel and color directly into the room of the watcher.

Hyrel had no way of seeing into the plastic affair she wore, but he guessed from the expression on the lower half of her face that she was watching one of the newer black-market sex-operas. In any event, there would be no sound, movement, or sign of life from her for the next three hours. To break the thread of the play for even a moment would ruin all the previous emotional build-up.

There had been a time when he hated her for those long and silent evenings, lonely hours during which he was completely ignored. It was different now, however, for those hours furnished him with time for an escape of his own.

His lips curled into a tight smile and his right hand fondled the unobtrusive switch beneath his trouser leg. He did not press the switch. He would wait a few minutes longer. But it was comforting to know that it was there, exhilarating to know that he could escape for a few hours by a mere flick of his finger.

He let his eyes stray to the dim light of the artificial flames in the fireplace. His hate for her was not bounded merely by those lonely hours she had forced upon him. No, it was far more encompassing.

He hated her with a deep, burning savagery that was deadly in its passion. He hated her for her money, the money she kept securely from him. He hated her for the paltry allowance she doled out to him, as if he were an irresponsible child. It was as if she were constantly reminding him in every glance and gesture, "I made a bad bargain when I married you. You wanted me, my money, everything, and had nothing to give in return except your own doltish self. You set a trap for me, baited with lies and a false front. Now you are caught in your own trap and will remain there like a mouse to eat from my hand whatever crumbs I stoop to give you."

But some day his hate would be appeased. Yes, some day soon he would kill her!

He shot a sideways glance at her, wondering if by chance she suspected.... She hadn't moved. Her lips were pouted into a half smile; the sex-opera had probably reached one of its more pleasurable moments.

Hyrel let his eyes shift back to the fireplace again. Yes, he would kill her. Then he would claim a rightful share of her money, be rid of her debasing dominance.

He let the thought run around through his head, savoring it with mental taste buds. He would not kill her tonight. No, nor the next night. He would wait, wait until he had sucked the last measure of pleasure from the thought.

It was like having a bottle of rare old wine on a shelf where it could be viewed daily. It was like being able to pause again and again before the bottle, hold it up to the light, and say to it, "Some day, when my desire for you has reached the ultimate, I shall unstopper you quietly and sip you slowly to the last soul-satisfying drop." As long as the bottle remained there upon the shelf it was symbolic of that pleasurable moment....

He snapped out of his reverie and realized he had been wasting precious moments. There would be time enough tomorrow for gloating. Tonight, there were other things to do. Pleasurable things. He remembered the girl he had met the night before, and smiled smugly. Perhaps she would be awaiting him even now. If not, there would be another one....

He settled himself deeper into the chair, glanced once more at his wife, then let his head lean comfortably back against the chair's headrest. His hand upon his thigh felt the thin mesh that cloaked his body beneath his clothing like a sheer stocking. His fingers went again to the tiny switch. Again he hesitated.

Herbert Hyrel knew no more about the telporter suit he wore than he did about the radio in the corner, the TV set against the wall, or the personalized telovis his wife was wearing. You pressed one of the buttons on the radio; music came out. You pressed a button and clicked a dial on the TV; music and pictures came out. You pressed a button and made an adjustment on the telovis; three-dimensional, emotion-colored pictures leaped into the room. You pressed a tiny switch on the telporter suit; you were whisked away to a receiving set you had previously set up in secret.

He knew that the music and the images of the performers on the TV and telovis were brought to his room by some form of electrical impulse or wave while the actual musicians and performers remained in the studio. He knew that when he pressed the switch on his thigh something within him—his ectoplasm, higher self, the thing spirits use for materialization, whatever its real name—streamed out of him along an invisible channel, leaving his body behind in the chair in a conscious but dream-like state. His other self materialized in a small cabin in a hidden nook between a highway and a river where he had installed the receiving set a month ago.

He thought once more of the girl who might be waiting for him, smiled, and pressed the switch.

The dank air of the cabin was chill to Herbert Hyrel's naked flesh. He fumbled through the darkness for the clothing he kept there, found his shorts and trousers, got hurriedly into them, then flicked on a pocket lighter and ignited a stub of candle upon the table. By the wavering light, he finished dressing in the black satin clothing, the white shirt, the flowing necktie and tam. He invoiced the contents of his billfold. Not much. And his monthly pittance was still two weeks away....

He had skimped for six months to salvage enough money from his allowance to make a down payment on the telporter suit. Since then, his expenses—monthly payments for the suit, cabin rent, costly liquor—had forced him to place his nights of escape on strict ration. He could not go on this way, he realized. Not now. Not since he had met the girl. He had to have more money. Perhaps he could not afford the luxury of leaving the wine bottle longer upon the shelf....

Riverside Club, where Hyrel arrived by bus and a hundred yards of walking, was exclusive. It catered to a clientele that had but three things in common: money, a desire for utter self-abandonment, and a sales slip indicating ownership of a telporter suit. The club was of necessity expensive, for self-telportation was strictly illegal, and police protection came high.

Herbert Hyrel adjusted his white, silken mask carefully at the door and shoved his sales slip through a small aperture where it was thoroughly scanned by unseen eyes. A buzzer sounded an instant later, the lock on the door clicked, and Hyrel pushed through into the exhilarating warmth of music and laughter.

The main room was large. Hidden lights along the walls sent slow beams of red, blue, vermillion, green, yellow and pink trailing across the domed ceiling in a heterogeneous pattern. The colored beams mingled, diffused, spread, were caught up by mirrors of various tints which diffused and mingled the lights once more until the whole effect was an ever-changing panorama of softly-melting shades.

The gay and bizarre costumes of the masked revelers on the dance floor and at the tables, unearthly in themselves, were made even more so by the altering light. Music flooded the room from unseen sources. Laughter—hysterical, drunken, filled with utter abandonment—came from the dance floor, the tables, and the private booths and rooms hidden cleverly within the walls.

Hyrel pushed himself to an unoccupied table, sat down and ordered a bottle of cheap whiskey. He would have preferred champagne, but his depleted finances forbade the more discriminate taste.

When his order arrived, he poured a glass tumbler half full and consumed it eagerly while his eyes scanned the room in search of the girl. He couldn't see her in the dim swirl of color. Had she arrived? Perhaps she was wearing a different costume than she had the night before. If so, recognition might prove difficult.

He poured himself another drink, promising himself he would go in search of her when the liquor began to take effect.

A woman clad in the revealing garb of a Persian dancer threw an arm about him from behind and kissed him on the cheek through the veil which covered the lower part of her face.

"Hi, honey," she giggled into his ear. "Havin' a time?"

He reached for the white arm to pull her to him, but she eluded his grasp and reeled away into the waiting arms of a tall toreador. Hyrel gulped his whiskey and watched her nestle into the arms of her partner and begin with him a sinuous, suggestive dance. The whiskey had begun its warming effect, and he laughed.

This was the land of the lotus eaters, the sanctuary of the escapists, the haven of all who wished to cast off their shell of inhibition and become the thing they dreamed themselves to be. Here one could be among his own kind, an actor upon a gay stage, a gaudy butterfly metamorphosed from the slug, a knight of old.

The Persian dancing girl was probably the wife of a boorish oaf whose idea of romance was spending an evening telling his wife how he came to be a successful bank president. But she had found her means of escape. Perhaps she had pleaded a sick headache and had retired to her room. And there upon the bed now reposed her shell of reality while her inner self, the shadowy one, completely materialized, became an exotic thing from the East in this never-never land.

The man, the toreador, had probably closeted himself within his library with a set of account books and had left strict orders not to be disturbed until he had finished with them.

Both would have terrific hangovers in the morning. But that, of course, would be fully compensated for by the memories of the evening.

Hyrel chuckled. The situation struck him as being funny: the shadowy self got drunk and had a good time, and the outer husk suffered the hangover in the morning. Strange. Strange how a device such as the telporter suit could cause the shadow of each bodily cell to leave the body, materialize, and become a reality in its own right. And yet ...

He looked at the heel of his left hand. There was a long, irregular scar there. It was the result of a cut he had received nearly three weeks ago when he had fallen over this very table and had rammed his hand into a sliver of broken champagne glass. Later that evening, upon re-telporting back home, the pain of the cut had remained in his hand, but there was no sign of the cut itself on the hand of his outer self. The scar was peculiar to the shadowy body only. There was something about the shadowy body that carried the hurts to the outer body, but not the scars....

Sudden laughter broke out near him, and he turned quickly in that direction. A group of gaily costumed revelers was standing in a semi-circle about a small mound of clothing upon the floor. It was the costume of the toreador.

Hyrel laughed, too. It had happened many times before—a costume suddenly left empty as its owner, due to a threat of discovery at home, had had to press the switch in haste to bring his shadowy self—and complete consciousness—back to his outer self in a hurry.

A waiter picked up the clothing. He would put it safely away so that the owner could claim it upon his next visit to the club. Another waiter placed a fresh bottle of whiskey on the table before Hyrel, and Hyrel paid him for it.

The whiskey, reaching his head now in surges of warm cheerfulness, was filling him with abandonment, courage, and a desire for merriment. He pushed himself up from the table, joined the merry throng, threw his arm about the Persian dancer, drew her close.

They began dancing slowly to the throbbing rhythm, dancing and holding on to each other tightly. Hyrel could feel her hot breath through her veil upon his neck, adding to the headiness of the liquor. His feeling of depression and inferiority flowed suddenly from him. Once again he was the all-conquering male.

His arm trembled as it drew her still closer to him and he began dancing directly and purposefully toward the shadows of a clump of artificial palms near one corner of the room. There was an exit to the garden behind the palms.

Half way there they passed a secluded booth from which protruded a long leg clad in black mesh stocking. Hyrel paused as he recognized that part of the costume. It was she! The girl! The one he had met so briefly the night before!

His arm slid away from the Persian dancer, took hold of the mesh-clad leg, and pulled. A female form followed the leg from the booth and fell into his arms. He held her tightly, kissed her white neck, let her perfume send his thoughts reeling.

"Been looking for me, honey?" she whispered, her voice deep and throaty.

"You know it!"

He began whisking her away toward the palms. The Persian girl was pulled into the booth.

Yes, she was wearing the same costume she had worn the night before, that of a can-can dancer of the 90's. The mesh hose that encased her shapely legs were held up by flowered supporters in such a manner as to leave four inches of white leg exposed between hose top and lacy panties. Her skirt, frilled to suggest innumerable petticoats, fell away at each hip, leaving the front open to expose the full length of legs. She wore a wig of platinum hair encrusted with jewels that sparkled in the lights. Her jewel-studded mask was as white as her hair and covered the upper half of her face, except for the large almond slits for her eyes. A white purse, jewel crusted, dangled from one arm.

He stopped once before reaching the palms, drew her closer, kissed her long and ardently. Then he began pulling her on again.

She drew back when they reached the shelter of the fronds. "Champagne, first," she whispered huskily into his ear.

His heart sank. He had very little money left. Well, it might buy a cheap brand....

She sipped her champagne slowly and provocatively across the table from him. Her eyes sparkled behind the almond slits of her mask, caught the color changes and cast them back. She was wearing contact lenses of a garish green.

He wished she would hurry with her drink. He had horrible visions of his wife at home taking off her telovis and coming to his chair. He would then have to press the switch that would jerk his shadowy self back along its invisible connecting cord, jerk him back and leave but a small mound of clothes upon the chair at the table.

Deep depression laid hold of him. He would not be able to see her after tonight until he received his monthly dole two weeks hence. She wouldn't wait that long. Someone else would have her.

Unless ...

Yes, he knew now that he was going to kill his wife as soon as the opportunity presented itself. It would be a simple matter. With the aid of the telporter suit, he could establish an iron-clad alibi.

He took a long drink of whiskey and looked at the dancers about him. Sight of their gay costumes heightened his depression. He was wearing a cheap suit of satin, all he could afford. But some day soon he would show them! Some time soon he would be dressed as gaily....

"Something troubling you, honey?"

His gaze shot back to her and she blurred slightly before his eyes. "No. Nothing at all!" He summoned a sickly smile and clutched her hand in his. "Come on. Let's dance."

He drew her from the chair and into his arms. She melted toward him as if desiring to become a part of him. A tremor of excitement surged through him and threatened to turn his knees into quivering jelly. He could not make his feet conform to the flooding rhythm of the music. He half stumbled, half pushed her along past the booths.

In the shelter of the palms he drew her savagely to him. "Let's—let's go outside." His voice was little more than a croak.

"But, honey!" She pushed herself away, her low voice maddening him. "Don't you have a private room? A girl doesn't like to be taken outside...."

Her words bit into his brain like the blade of a hot knife.

No, he didn't have a private room at the club like the others. A private room for his telporter receiver, a private room where he could take a willing guest. No! He couldn't afford it! No! No! NO! His lot was a cheap suit of satin! Cheap whiskey! Cheap champagne! A cheap shack by the river....

An inarticulate cry escaped his twisted lips. He clutched her roughly to him and dragged her through the door and into the moonlight, whiskey and anger lending him brutal strength.

He pulled her through the deserted garden. All the others had private rooms! He pulled her to the far end, behind a clump of squatty firs. His hands clawed at her. He tried to smother her mouth with kisses.

She eluded him deftly. "But, honey!" Her voice had gone deeper into her throat. "I just want to be sure about things. If you can't afford one of the private rooms—if you can't afford to show me a good time—if you can't come here real often ..."

The whiskey pounded and throbbed at his brain like blows from an unseen club. His ego curled and twisted within him like a headless serpent.

"I'll have money!" he shouted, struggling to hold her. "I'll have plenty of money! After tonight!"

"Then we'll wait," she said. "We'll wait until tomorrow night."

"No!" he screamed. "You don't believe me! You're like the others! You think I'm no good! But I'll show you! I'll show all of you!"

She had gone coldly rigid in his arms, unyielding.

Madness added to the pounding in his brain. Tears welled into his eyes.

"I'll show you! I'll kill her! Then I'll have money!" The hands clutching her shoulders shook her drunkenly. "You wait here! I'll go home and kill her now! Then I'll be back!"

"Silly boy!" Her low laughter rang hollowly in his ears. "And just who is it you are going to kill?"

"My wife!" he cried. "My wife! I'll ..."

A sudden sobering thought struck him. He was talking too much. And he wasn't making sense. He shouldn't be telling her this. Anyway, he couldn't get the money tonight even if he did kill his wife.

"And so you are going to kill your wife...."

He blinked the tears from his eyes. His chest was heaving, his heart pounding. He looked at her shimmering form. "Y-yes," he whispered.

Her eyes glinted strangely in the light of the moon. Her handbag glinted as she opened it, and something she took from it glittered coldly in her hand.

"Fool!"

The first shot tore squarely through his heart. And while he stood staring at her, mouth agape, a second shot burned its way through his bewildered brain.

Mrs. Herbert Hyrel removed the telovis from her head and laid it carefully aside. She uncoiled her long legs from beneath her, walked to her husband's chair, and stood for a long moment looking down at him, her lips drawn back in contempt. Then she bent over him and reached down his thigh until her fingers contacted the small switch.

Seconds later, a slight tremor shook Hyrel's body. His eyes snapped open, air escaped his lungs, his lower jaw sagged inanely, and his head lolled to one side.

She stood a moment longer, watching his eyes become glazed and sightless. Then she walked to the telephone.

"Police?" she said. "This is Mrs. Herbert Hyrel. Something horrible has happened to my husband. Please come over immediately. Bring a doctor."

She hung up, went to her bathroom, stripped off her clothing, and slid carefully out of her telporter suit. This she folded neatly and tucked away into the false back of the medicine cabinet. She found a fresh pair of blue, plastifur pajamas and got into them.

She was just arriving back into the living room, tying the cord of her dressing gown about her slim waist, when she heard the sound of the police siren out front.

2023-08-28 03:11:40 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-08-28 03:11:41 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-08-28 03:11:43 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-08-28 03:11:44 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:47 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:48 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:49 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:11:51 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:11:52 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:11:53 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-08-28 03:12:14 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-08-28 03:12:15 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-08-28 03:12:15 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@2d706ff3